"lang"
{
	"Language"		"English"
	"Tokens"
	{		
		"addonname"									"Training Polygon"
		"mapTitle"   								"Manta evasion training"
		"menuMods"    								"MODS:"
		"menuInfo"    								"INFO:"
		"mantaInfo"    								"This training is designed to hone the skill of dodging spells with Manta Style. Some day it will save your character's life. Using Manta Style your character became hidden, invulnerable and magic immune for 0.1 seconds. Also your character dodge any auto-attacks upon cast and most of projectile skills. The list on the right shows abilities that not disjoints by using Manta Style, AOE abilities that can be avoided, also some abilities which effect your character over time. There are no abilities with small cast time(<0.1 sec, ex. Sand King's Burrow Strike), because dodging depends mostly on luck. Maybe you watched a video on which Arteezy breaking Dream Coil with Manta Style. This trick is hard to train cause of its randomness. Using manta creates 2 illusion on 4 random directions(north,west,south,east), with which hero randomly swaps(or not). So if u want to leave Dream Coil without stunning, you should stand on the edge and use Manta, but chance of success is to small. If u want to know more about Manta Style mechanics visit wiki page:"
		"menuSet"    								"SETTINGS:"
		"menuTimebar"    							"Toggle timebar"
		"menuSkills"    							"Choose skills:"
		"menuSkill"    								"Choose skill:"
		"skillsAll"    								"Select All"
		"skillsNone"    							"Unmark All"
		"menuStart"    								"Start training"
		"menuErr"    								"You should choose at least one skill!!!"
		"timebarTooltip"    						"Timebar is panel, that helps with timing."
		"trainingEnd"    							"End training"
		"inARow"    								"In a row:"
		"mantaGood"    								"Good!"
		"mantaBad"    								"Bad!"
		"eulsTitle"									"Eul's scepter training"
		"notifyPerfect"								"Perfect!"
		"eulInfo1"									"This mode is intended for training combination of Eul's scepter of divinity with abilities. Perfect timing in using Eul with high damage abilities, stuns or silences increases your chances of winning. If you not train this skill, you can miss your ability."
		"eulInfo2"									"I made a list of escape abilities for example:"
		"eulInfo3"									"Based on this list, good result is 0.2 seconds between landing and effect of ability. Anyway, I advise you to train until you can produce a result of 0.1 second without timebar."
		"eulTimeBarInfo"							"You should use ability when bar reach green zone"
		"eulEarly"									"Too early :'("
		"eulLate"									"Too late =("
		"eulDesc"									"Time between landing and ability: "
		"welcomeOne"								"Hello, %username%. I hope you will enjoy this gamemode. In this moment i have no job, and i need money for upgrade my shitty pc and for development of this map. The release of new updates is complicated by constant reloads, application errors and blue screens of death. <b>I dont want to make paid features, so I ask you to help than you can.</b> If I collect a sufficient amount, I will introduce many new modes, add a leaderboard and weekly challanges with prizes. I hope for your understanding and wish you all the best."
		"welcomeTwo"								"Methods of material support are indicated on the page in the workshop. Donations list updates every 12-24 hours."
		"welcomeButton"								"Cool story"
		"welcomeTitle"								"Welcome to the training polygon!"
		"eulBBdesc"									"When you train this skill, you first use ability, and then the Eul."
		"eulDescOne"								"Skills with a specific timings:"
		"eulDescTwo"								"Dynamic Timing Skills:"
		"eulDescTwoTT"								"Тhe timbar does not work with these abilities, since the ideal timing depends on the distance between the hero and the target"
		"teleportMode"								"Teleport mode:"
		"tpModeOne"									"Every 5 kills"
		"tpModeTwo"									"Teleport only"
		"tpModeThree"								"No teleport"
		"tpReminder"								"Use Boots of Travel!"
		"glimpseInfo1"								"This mode is created for the practice of evasion from Glimpse. You must kill Disruptors and try to evade Glimpse. Here is description of Glimpse mechanic:"
		"glimpseInfo2"								"-In the point where the target was located 4 seconds ago, a blue effect is created;"
		"glimpseInfo3"								"-From the target to the point of return projectile start movement at a speed of 600, or 1.8 seconds, if the flight distance exceeds 1080;"
		"glimpseInfo4"								"-On projectile reach the return point, if target doesnt have spell immune it will be rellocated to the return point;"
		"glimpseInfo5"								"Since Glimpse can not move a target that is immune to magic, the movement effect can be avoided with artifacts: Black King Bar and Manta Style, as well as a large number of abilities that give magical invulnerability. In this training, the most difficult to perform abilities are presented, since the time to which magical invulnerability is given is extremely small."
		"glimpseInfo6"								"The list of available abilities for the complexity of performance, starting with the simplest:"
		"glimpseInfo7"								"Cast point: 0.1 s, magic immune duration 1 s."
		"glimpseInfo8"								"Cast point: 0.4 s, magic immune duration 0.5 s."
		"glimpseInfo9"								"Cast point: 0.65 s, magic immune duration 0.3 s."
		"glimpseInfo10"								"Cast point: 0 s, magic immune duration 0.2 s (for each target)."
		"glimpseInfo11"								"Cast point: 0 s, magic immune duration 0.1 s."
		"glimpseInfo12"								"The teleport mode is designed to train the dodge from Glimpse after teleportation, because The flight time of the projectile will almost always be 1.8 s."
		"glimpseInfo13"								"Green zone of timebar is calculated by (castpoint)+((mag. immune time)/2)."
		"donAllTime"								"Top donations all time:"
		"donLastTen"								"Last 10 donations:"
		"donTopMonth"								"Top donations this month"
		"donFirst"									"First donation ever:"
		"bankaSelf"									"Self cast dodge training. Practicing separately."
		"translationProvided"						"Translated by:"
		"eulArts"									"Additional items:"
	}
}
