"lang"
{
	"Language"		"English"
	"Tokens"
	{		
		"addonname"									"Training Polygon"
		"mapTitle"   								"Manta evasion training"
		"menuMods"    								"MODS:"
		"menuInfo"    								"INFO:"
		"mantaInfo"    								"Since its not only Manta training, i decided to remove old description that was here. Everything is simple. Choose way to dodge abilities (some of them may not work properly, sorry), then choose some options (maybe you wanna harder, maybe easier) and then choose skills that you wanna dodge. Why there is not all skills from dota 2? Because there is only undisjointable target skills (which means that you if you blinks or somehow change your position they will follow you) and aoe skills."
		"menuSet"    								"SETTINGS:"
		"menuTimebar"    							"Toggle timebar"
		"menuSkills"    							"Choose skills:"
		"menuSkill"    								"Choose skill:"
		"skillsAll"    								"Select All"
		"skillsNone"    							"Unmark All"
		"menuStart"    								"Start training"
		"menuErr"    								"You should choose at least one skill!!!"
		"timebarTooltip"    						"Timebar is panel, that helps with timing."
		"trainingEnd"    							"End training"
		"inARow"    								"In a row:"
		"mantaGood"    								"Good!"
		"mantaBad"    								"Bad!"
		"eulsTitle"									"Eul's scepter training"
		"notifyPerfect"								"Perfect!"
		"eulInfo1"									"This mode is intended for training combination of Eul's scepter of divinity with abilities. Perfect timing in using Eul with high damage abilities, stuns or silences increases your chances of winning. If you not train this skill, you can miss your ability."
		"eulInfo2"									"I made a list of escape abilities for example:"
		"eulInfo3"									"Based on this list, good result is 0.2 seconds between landing and effect of ability. Anyway, I advise you to train until you can produce a result of 0.1 second without timebar."
		"eulTimeBarInfo"							"You should use ability when bar reach green zone"
		"eulEarly"									"Too early :'("
		"eulLate"									"Too late =("
		"eulDesc"									"Time between landing and ability: "
		"welcomeOne"								"Hello, %username%. I hope you will enjoy this gamemode. In this moment i have no job, and i need money for upgrade my shitty pc and for development of this map. The release of new updates is complicated by constant reloads, application errors and blue screens of death. <b>I dont want to make paid features, so I ask you to help than you can.</b> If I collect a sufficient amount, I will introduce many new modes, add a leaderboard and weekly challanges with prizes. I hope for your understanding and wish you all the best."
		"welcomeTwo"								"Methods of material support are indicated on the page in the workshop. Donations list updates every 12-24 hours."
		"welcomeButton"								"Cool story"
		"welcomeTitle"								"Welcome to the training polygon!"
		"eulBBdesc"									"When you train this skill, you first use ability, and then the Eul."
		"eulDescOne"								"Skills with a specific timings:"
		"eulDescTwo"								"Dynamic Timing Skills:"
		"eulDescTwoTT"								"Тhe timbar does not work with these abilities, since the ideal timing depends on the distance between the hero and the target"
		"teleportMode"								"Teleport mode:"
		"tpModeOne"									"Every 5 kills"
		"tpModeTwo"									"Teleport only"
		"tpModeThree"								"No teleport"
		"tpReminder"								"Use Boots of Travel!"
		"glimpseInfo1"								"This mode is created for the practice of evasion from Glimpse. You must kill Disruptors and try to evade Glimpse. Here is description of Glimpse mechanic:"
		"glimpseInfo2"								"-In the point where the target was located 4 seconds ago, a blue effect is created;"
		"glimpseInfo3"								"-From the target to the point of return projectile start movement at a speed of 600, or 1.8 seconds, if the flight distance exceeds 1080;"
		"glimpseInfo4"								"-On projectile reach the return point, if target doesnt have spell immune it will be rellocated to the return point;"
		"glimpseInfo5"								"Since Glimpse can not move a target that is immune to magic, the movement effect can be avoided with artifacts: Black King Bar and Manta Style, as well as a large number of abilities that give magical invulnerability. In this training, the most difficult to perform abilities are presented, since the time to which magical invulnerability is given is extremely small."
		"glimpseInfo6"								"The list of available abilities for the complexity of performance, starting with the simplest:"
		"glimpseInfo7"								"Cast point: 0.1 s, magic immune duration 1 s."
		"glimpseInfo8"								"Cast point: 0.4 s, magic immune duration 0.5 s."
		"glimpseInfo9"								"Cast point: 0.65 s, magic immune duration 0.3 s."
		"glimpseInfo10"								"Cast point: 0 s, magic immune duration 0.2 s (for each target)."
		"glimpseInfo11"								"Cast point: 0 s, magic immune duration 0.1 s."
		"glimpseInfo12"								"The teleport mode is designed to train the dodge from Glimpse after teleportation, because The flight time of the projectile will almost always be 1.8 s."
		"glimpseInfo13"								"Green zone of timebar is calculated by (castpoint)+((mag. immune time)/2)."
		"donAllTime"								"Top donators all time:"
		"donLastTen"								"Last 10 donations:"
		"donTopMonth"								"Top donations this month"
		"donFirst"									"First donation ever:"
		"bankaSelf"									"Self cast dodge training. Practicing separately."
		"translationProvided"						"Translated by:"
		"eulArts"									"Additional items:"
		"shuffleMode"								"Shuffle skills"
		"hardcoreMode"								"Hardcore mode"
		"timingType"								"Choose type:"
		"armletSettings1"							"Choose attacking unit:"
		"armletInfo1"								"Now its training with one unit which attack speed and damage are adjustable. More options like adding skills, or choosing multiple units will come in next updates. If u have an interesting ideas or something that you want to see here so much, leave it on workshop page, and maybe i will add this."
		"armEnemy"									"ENEMY:"
		"armAttackSpeed"							"Attack speed:"
		"armDamage"									"Damage:"
		"armFakeMode"								"Fake mode:"
		"twitchMsg"									"I brought back links from boosty/patreon, if there will be total 200 subs, i'll add some bonuses for subs, sorry for not posting stuff on patreon/boosty it is so hard for me to do it:"
		"lb_highscore"								"New high score!"
		"lb_nothighscore"							"Nice try."
		"lb_last_result"							"Your last result was {s:last_result}. Better luck next time."
		"lb_place"									"You scored: {s:score}. Your place is {s:place} of {s:total}. Congratulations!"
		"lb_return"									"Return to menu"
		"lb_try_again"								"Try again"
		"loadingExplain"	"Since now we need separately precache players items for heroes, we do it now and have to wait a bit. You can play game below if you have ADHD."
		"welcome2019"	"Hi， %username%! Im really trying to do my best, but GabeN and IceFrog always broke this game. Hope you enjoy."
		"armInfo"								"I trying to make it better but dont know how."
		"tLiveStatus"	"LIVE"
		"tGame"	"Game:"
		"playersCounter"	"Unique players this month"
		"mods_manta"	"Abilities dodging"
		"mods_eul"	"Training of abilities timing"
		"mods_glimpse"	"Training of Glimpse evasion"
		"mods_armlet"	"Armlet toggle training"
		"mods_aim"	"Mouse aim training"
		"mods_invoker"	"Invoker training"
		"mods_skillshot"	"Skillshots training"
		"mods_other"	"Other stuff"
		"mods_last_hit"	"Lasthit training"
		"mods_chalange"	"Challenges"
		"other_info"	"I made this tab because i know that you wanna make a perfect Kunkka's combo"
		"lasthit_info"	"Just a lasthit training"
		"leaderboard_friends"	"Friends only"
		"aim_info"	"its a hidden stuff"
		"inv_info"	"Maybe it is not obvious, but in invoke practice when it ask to cast Alacrity or Forged spirit, you should attack target to complete this spell. If you wanna see some other combos leave suggestions on workshop page."
		"other_timebar"	"Choose combo:"
		"manta_options"	"Options:"
		"timingRubick"	"Rubick mode"
		"timingNobot"	"Without bot"
		"glimpse_level"	"Level:"
		"lasthit_side"	"Choose side"
		"lasthit_radiant"	"Radiant"
		"lasthit_dire"	"Dire"
		"lasthit_hero"	"Choose hero:"
		"lasthit_items"	"Choose items:"
		"lasthit_gold"	"Remaining gold"
		"invoker_invoke"	"Invoke Practice"
		"invoker_single_target"	"Single target"
		"invoker_one_sphere"	"One sphere mode"
		"invoker_combos"	"Combos:"
		"aim_challenge"	"Aim challenge"
		"map_aim_challenge"	"Map aim challenge"
		"move_aim_challenge"	"Aim challenge moving targets"
		"manta_challenge"	"Manta challenge"
		"invoker_challenge"	"Invoker challenge"
		"popup_title"	"Nice try!"
		"loading_name"	"lodaing"
		"t1"	"Trophy given for 1th place in this mode at the end of the week"
		"t2"	"Trophy given for 2nd place in this mode at the end of the week"
		"t3"	"Trophy given for 3rd place in this mode at the end of the week"
		"t4"	"Trophy given for 4th place in this mode at the end of the week"
		"t5"	"Trophy given for 5th place in this mode at the end of the week"
		"t100"	"Trophy given for top 100 place in this mode at the end of the week"
		"DOTA_TOOLTIP_ABILITY_ITEM_TOPOR" "Observer wards cutter"
		"DOTA_TOOLTIP_ABILITY_ITEM_TOPOR2" "Sentry wards cutter"
		"unableToTime" "Unable to properly precast this spell"
		"waitingForCastEnd" "Waiting for cast end"
		"moveSpeed" "Bonus movespeed:"
		"spiritBreakerTimebar" "Timebar is not calculating timing properly, maybe will be fixed in future"
	}
}
